# Michaela W. Freeman

8012 Wickers Villa Blvd., Unit 486, Lane, Biloxi, MS 39530 mwfreeman@umail.com (228) 000-1234

Disciplined, observant Homeland Security Officer with over a year of experience in ensuring a safe, comfortable experience for thousands of airport patrons. Able to communicate professionally and positively with associates and travelers of diverse backgrounds and needs. Tactfully and firmly enforces safety guidelines to facilitate movement and confront suspicious behavior.

### **Education**

Associate of Applied Science in Criminal Justice Mississippi Gulf Coast Community College Biloxi, MS September 2016 - April 2018

High School Diploma Booker T. Washington High School Pensacola, FL, 2016

## **Key Skills**

- Safety and security
- Self-motivated
- ♦ Team player
- Customer service
- ♦ Fast learner

#### **Credentials**

♦ Mississippi Security Guard Permit -renewed 12/17/19

## **Professional Experience**

Transportation Security Officer

Department of Homeland Security, Gulfport, MS | May 2019 - Present

- Performing physical screening and searches of passengers and their bags at Gulfport-Biloxi International Airport
- Responding to passenger inquiries and giving directions
- Operating screening equipment to identify and prevent dangerous objects from being carried onto aircraft
- Patrolling terminal entry and exit points
- Awarded certificate for exemplary team spirit and customer service

#### Campus Police Security Officer

Singing River Health System, Gulfport, MS | April 2018 - April 2019

- Patrolled hospital buildings and premises to deter intruders, theft and vandalism
- Monitored conduct of visitors
- Assisted in restraints of psychiatric patients and uncooperative guests as needed
- Responded to code calls in emergency situations